<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string-array name="type_of_betting_strategies">
        <item>1X on home outsiders strategy</item>
        <item>All-in on odds at 1.20 strategy</item>
        <!--        <item>The 1–3–2-6 system</item>-->
        <item>The Fibonacci betting system</item>
        <item>Betting on late goals</item>
        <item>What’s a Money Race?</item>
        <item>Early cashout in sports betting</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="description_of_the_betting_strategies">
        <item>  A betting strategy that has been successful
            in the past is the bet on the “double chance” 1X if an outsider plays
            against a favorite at home. In this case, the “1X” bet brings respectable
            odds and very interesting profit opportunities.\n
            \n

                You don’t even have to choose and analyze games that contain absolute
            extremes and obvious class differences with this strategy.
            So, you don’t necessarily have to bet against Barcelona, Bayern or Juventus
            as an away team. Here, we would probably move away from the value bets.
            Even if we opt for teams that are not big outsiders, but are still outsiders according to the odds,
            we find highly interesting odds between 1.60 and 2.50.
           </item>
        <item>  This betting strategy involves winning numerous bets one after the other and always
            using the maximum offers the opportunity to earn decent money. But it is also clear
            that all the money is gone if you lose a bet. But if you manage to win 30, 35, maybe
            even 40 times in a row, you’ll get big money!\n
            \n

                We use odds around 1.20 for this – ideally you should look for the bets you are playing
            live. As with the strategy of betting over 1.5 goals in what is estimated to be typical
            “over” games, you can wait here until the odds have reached the desired level.
            The over 0.5 bet is ideal here – i.e. the bet that the game will not end 0-0. Usually,
            after goalless 30 minutes, you get a rate of 1.20 – depending on the match, this can
            of course be lower, but sometimes even higher. Of course, it is a matter of taste
            with which type of bet you want to monetize your betting sequence,
            or money race‘ as it is also called.
        </item>
        <item>  The 1-3-2-6 system is similar to another positive progression betting system known
            as a Paroli. Both involve increased stakes after a win, and both involve a cycle of bets
            ending at a fixed point. The only real difference is the actual betting sequence.\n
            \n

                Like many betting systems, the 1-3-2-6 was designed for bets that pay out an even sum,
            like the red-black bets in roulette. In fact, it is widely used on the roulette table
            and in other casino games such as baccarat, dice games and blackjack. Basically,
            it doesn’t matter what you use it for, provided you are playing with even sums.
        </item>
        <item>  The Fibonacci betting system is one of many betting strategies available today.
            Fibonacci sequence betting is undoubtedly a controversial concept. But there are
            definitely sports bettors who were able to achieve great success with it. This strategy
            carries some risks, but with the necessary luck and the right nose, you can be
            successful while employing this strategy.\n
            \n

                The basic concept of betting according to the Fibonacci sequence is simple: bet
            on a tie. If you lose, just bet on the next tie according to a certain key and
            start increasing your stake.
            </item>
        <item>For example in relation to late goals betting, look for games with a clear favourite
            with 3-way winning odds of less than 1.30. In a betting round, spread the risk over
            as many games as possible; obviously, there will always be some unexpected losses.
            Then, bet on late goals for each of these games. Most bookmakers offer these bets under
            the name “Last goal will be in minutes 76-90”. Statistically, you will win just under
            60% of all of these bets.

        </item>
        <item>  A money race is a betting strategy in which the profit amount from a winning bet is
            invested directly in the next bet. This is usually continued through numerous bets until
            a desired amount of money is reached.\n
            \n

                The Money Race can be run with all possible types of bets. In most cases, however,
            the focus is specifically on low odds and thus “safe bets”, in order to win as many
            bets as possible in a row. In this case, the Money Race is particularly interesting
            for sports bettors with a high bankroll. If the Money Race is started with a rather
            high initial stake, you will save yourself numerous necessary profits on the way to
            the self-imposed goal. At the same time, however, the risk of loss is also greater.
        </item>
        <item>  Have you ever regretted placing a particular bet and wished that you could somehow
            withdraw it? Or maybe you had doubts as to whether the team you supported could really
            hold the lead? If your answer to any of the questions is yes, then you’ll love the early
            withdrawal option. These properties give the speculator more control over the bets
            already placed and could ultimately make a big difference in the overall bankroll if
            you wager your cards correctly. The early payout is often referred to as the cashout by
            most sports betting sites.\n
            \n

                If the team or player you are supporting is in a winning position but is being led out
            by the opponent, then you should definitely make a cashout and secure the appropriate
            profit instead of watching your potential profit and stake vanish into thin air. Your
            forecast proves correct and your choices lose the lead.
        </item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="urls">
        <item>https://img.championat.com/s/735x490/news/big/c/w/knigi-o-stavkah-na-sport_15892350831281582369.jpg</item>
        <item>https://football-match24.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/09/stavki-online.jpg</item>
        <item>https://sportyakutia.ru/images/1fotoposel/1posel2020/aug21/stavki-na-sport.jpg</item>
        <item>https://www.calc.ru/imgs/articles3/13/85/102075582e171b533a98.28838079.jpg</item>
        <item>https://lifebet.ru/sites/default/files/kak-delat-stavki-na-sport.jpg</item>
        <item>https://jurnalstroy.ru/wp-content/uploads/2021/10/sports-betting.jpg</item>
    </string-array>



</resources>